[{"subjectID":"n9x4mlaxxe","prolificID":"5c4d8d706b23ab0001a34af2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24a45b646cd717dedaf","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980664697,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":0,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"245","question":"What is the most sophisticated piece of technology or machinery you understand? How did you learn about it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":72,"rt":41870,"timeElapsed":375843},{"subjectID":"n9x4mlaxxe","prolificID":"5c4d8d706b23ab0001a34af2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24a45b646cd717dedaf","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980670116,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":1,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"245","question":"What is the most sophisticated piece of technology or machinery you understand? How did you learn about it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":34,"rt":5415,"timeElapsed":381263},{"subjectID":"n9x4mlaxxe","prolificID":"5c4d8d706b23ab0001a34af2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24a45b646cd717dedaf","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980676394,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":2,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"245","question":"What is the most sophisticated piece of technology or machinery you understand? How did you learn about it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":4,"rt":6273,"timeElapsed":387541},{"subjectID":"n9x4mlaxxe","prolificID":"5c4d8d706b23ab0001a34af2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24a45b646cd717dedaf","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980733734,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":3,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"245","question":"What is the most sophisticated piece of technology or machinery you understand? How did you learn about it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":57335,"timeElapsed":444881},{"subjectID":"n9x4mlaxxe","prolificID":"5c4d8d706b23ab0001a34af2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24a45b646cd717dedaf","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980774425,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":4,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"245","question":"What is the most sophisticated piece of technology or machinery you understand? How did you learn about it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":40685,"timeElapsed":485571},{"subjectID":"n9x4mlaxxe","prolificID":"5c4d8d706b23ab0001a34af2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24a45b646cd717dedaf","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980830100,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":5,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"245","question":"What is the most sophisticated piece of technology or machinery you understand? How did you learn about it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":36,"rt":55672,"timeElapsed":541247},{"subjectID":"n9x4mlaxxe","prolificID":"5c4d8d706b23ab0001a34af2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24a45b646cd717dedaf","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980836988,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":6,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"245","question":"What is the most sophisticated piece of technology or machinery you understand? How did you learn about it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":43,"rt":6882,"timeElapsed":548135},{"subjectID":"n9x4mlaxxe","prolificID":"5c4d8d706b23ab0001a34af2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24a45b646cd717dedaf","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980889211,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":7,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"245","question":"What is the most sophisticated piece of technology or machinery you understand? How did you learn about it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":25,"rt":52219,"timeElapsed":600358},{"subjectID":"n9x4mlaxxe","prolificID":"5c4d8d706b23ab0001a34af2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24a45b646cd717dedaf","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980896028,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":8,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"245","question":"What is the most sophisticated piece of technology or machinery you understand? How did you learn about it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":36,"rt":6812,"timeElapsed":607175},{"subjectID":"n9x4mlaxxe","prolificID":"5c4d8d706b23ab0001a34af2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24a45b646cd717dedaf","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980975052,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":9,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"215","question":"Is there anybody (a famous person or someone you know) that you’ve learned to do an impression of? How did you learn this? Who did you most recently show this to?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":77203,"timeElapsed":686198},{"subjectID":"n9x4mlaxxe","prolificID":"5c4d8d706b23ab0001a34af2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24a45b646cd717dedaf","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980985388,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":10,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"215","question":"Is there anybody (a famous person or someone you know) that you’ve learned to do an impression of? How did you learn this? Who did you most recently show this to?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":10333,"timeElapsed":696535},{"subjectID":"n9x4mlaxxe","prolificID":"5c4d8d706b23ab0001a34af2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24a45b646cd717dedaf","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980989468,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":11,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"215","question":"Is there anybody (a famous person or someone you know) that you’ve learned to do an impression of? How did you learn this? Who did you most recently show this to?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":4075,"timeElapsed":700615},{"subjectID":"n9x4mlaxxe","prolificID":"5c4d8d706b23ab0001a34af2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24a45b646cd717dedaf","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981000684,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":12,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"215","question":"Is there anybody (a famous person or someone you know) that you’ve learned to do an impression of? How did you learn this? Who did you most recently show this to?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":37,"rt":11211,"timeElapsed":711831},{"subjectID":"n9x4mlaxxe","prolificID":"5c4d8d706b23ab0001a34af2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24a45b646cd717dedaf","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981004156,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":13,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"215","question":"Is there anybody (a famous person or someone you know) that you’ve learned to do an impression of? How did you learn this? Who did you most recently show this to?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":30,"rt":3468,"timeElapsed":715303},{"subjectID":"n9x4mlaxxe","prolificID":"5c4d8d706b23ab0001a34af2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24a45b646cd717dedaf","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981029364,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":14,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"215","question":"Is there anybody (a famous person or someone you know) that you’ve learned to do an impression of? How did you learn this? Who did you most recently show this to?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":6,"rt":25205,"timeElapsed":740511},{"subjectID":"n9x4mlaxxe","prolificID":"5c4d8d706b23ab0001a34af2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24a45b646cd717dedaf","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981034426,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":15,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"215","question":"Is there anybody (a famous person or someone you know) that you’ve learned to do an impression of? How did you learn this? Who did you most recently show this to?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":22,"rt":5057,"timeElapsed":745573},{"subjectID":"n9x4mlaxxe","prolificID":"5c4d8d706b23ab0001a34af2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24a45b646cd717dedaf","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981042764,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":16,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"215","question":"Is there anybody (a famous person or someone you know) that you’ve learned to do an impression of? How did you learn this? Who did you most recently show this to?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":44,"rt":8335,"timeElapsed":753911},{"subjectID":"n9x4mlaxxe","prolificID":"5c4d8d706b23ab0001a34af2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24a45b646cd717dedaf","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981046611,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":17,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"215","question":"Is there anybody (a famous person or someone you know) that you’ve learned to do an impression of? How did you learn this? Who did you most recently show this to?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":42,"rt":3842,"timeElapsed":757758},{"subjectID":"n9x4mlaxxe","prolificID":"5c4d8d706b23ab0001a34af2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24a45b646cd717dedaf","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981061514,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":18,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"196","question":"What was your favorite board game growing up or currently?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":13626,"timeElapsed":772661},{"subjectID":"n9x4mlaxxe","prolificID":"5c4d8d706b23ab0001a34af2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24a45b646cd717dedaf","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981069634,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":19,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"196","question":"What was your favorite board game growing up or currently?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":8116,"timeElapsed":780781},{"subjectID":"n9x4mlaxxe","prolificID":"5c4d8d706b23ab0001a34af2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24a45b646cd717dedaf","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981077501,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":20,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"196","question":"What was your favorite board game growing up or currently?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":13,"rt":7863,"timeElapsed":788648},{"subjectID":"n9x4mlaxxe","prolificID":"5c4d8d706b23ab0001a34af2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24a45b646cd717dedaf","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981114953,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":21,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"196","question":"What was your favorite board game growing up or currently?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":4,"rt":37449,"timeElapsed":826100},{"subjectID":"n9x4mlaxxe","prolificID":"5c4d8d706b23ab0001a34af2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24a45b646cd717dedaf","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981119163,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":22,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"196","question":"What was your favorite board game growing up or currently?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":11,"rt":4207,"timeElapsed":830310},{"subjectID":"n9x4mlaxxe","prolificID":"5c4d8d706b23ab0001a34af2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24a45b646cd717dedaf","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981127518,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":23,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"196","question":"What was your favorite board game growing up or currently?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":12,"rt":8350,"timeElapsed":838665},{"subjectID":"n9x4mlaxxe","prolificID":"5c4d8d706b23ab0001a34af2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24a45b646cd717dedaf","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981131945,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":24,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"196","question":"What was your favorite board game growing up or currently?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":13,"rt":4423,"timeElapsed":843091},{"subjectID":"n9x4mlaxxe","prolificID":"5c4d8d706b23ab0001a34af2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24a45b646cd717dedaf","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981140938,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":25,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"196","question":"What was your favorite board game growing up or currently?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":53,"rt":8989,"timeElapsed":852085},{"subjectID":"n9x4mlaxxe","prolificID":"5c4d8d706b23ab0001a34af2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24a45b646cd717dedaf","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981147638,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":26,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"196","question":"What was your favorite board game growing up or currently?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":52,"rt":6696,"timeElapsed":858785},{"subjectID":"n9x4mlaxxe","prolificID":"5c4d8d706b23ab0001a34af2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24a45b646cd717dedaf","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981221491,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":27,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"90","question":"What kinds of predicaments are you best at giving advice about?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":72768,"timeElapsed":932637},{"subjectID":"n9x4mlaxxe","prolificID":"5c4d8d706b23ab0001a34af2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24a45b646cd717dedaf","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981224484,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":28,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"90","question":"What kinds of predicaments are you best at giving advice about?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":81,"rt":2990,"timeElapsed":935631},{"subjectID":"n9x4mlaxxe","prolificID":"5c4d8d706b23ab0001a34af2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24a45b646cd717dedaf","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981230758,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":29,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"90","question":"What kinds of predicaments are you best at giving advice about?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":35,"rt":6270,"timeElapsed":941905},{"subjectID":"n9x4mlaxxe","prolificID":"5c4d8d706b23ab0001a34af2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24a45b646cd717dedaf","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981247094,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":30,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"90","question":"What kinds of predicaments are you best at giving advice about?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":46,"rt":16333,"timeElapsed":958241},{"subjectID":"n9x4mlaxxe","prolificID":"5c4d8d706b23ab0001a34af2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24a45b646cd717dedaf","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981259717,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":31,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"90","question":"What kinds of predicaments are you best at giving advice about?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":40,"rt":12619,"timeElapsed":970864},{"subjectID":"n9x4mlaxxe","prolificID":"5c4d8d706b23ab0001a34af2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24a45b646cd717dedaf","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981264876,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":32,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"90","question":"What kinds of predicaments are you best at giving advice about?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":8,"rt":5156,"timeElapsed":976023},{"subjectID":"n9x4mlaxxe","prolificID":"5c4d8d706b23ab0001a34af2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24a45b646cd717dedaf","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981267997,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":33,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"90","question":"What kinds of predicaments are you best at giving advice about?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":12,"rt":3118,"timeElapsed":979144},{"subjectID":"n9x4mlaxxe","prolificID":"5c4d8d706b23ab0001a34af2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24a45b646cd717dedaf","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981273715,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":34,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"90","question":"What kinds of predicaments are you best at giving advice about?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":13,"rt":5715,"timeElapsed":984862},{"subjectID":"n9x4mlaxxe","prolificID":"5c4d8d706b23ab0001a34af2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24a45b646cd717dedaf","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981277338,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":35,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"90","question":"What kinds of predicaments are you best at giving advice about?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":11,"rt":3619,"timeElapsed":988485},{"subjectID":"n9x4mlaxxe","prolificID":"5c4d8d706b23ab0001a34af2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24a45b646cd717dedaf","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981289529,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":36,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"8","question":"Name three things you and your closest friend or partner have in common.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":10537,"timeElapsed":1000675},{"subjectID":"n9x4mlaxxe","prolificID":"5c4d8d706b23ab0001a34af2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24a45b646cd717dedaf","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981292264,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":37,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"8","question":"Name three things you and your closest friend or partner have in common.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":81,"rt":2732,"timeElapsed":1003411},{"subjectID":"n9x4mlaxxe","prolificID":"5c4d8d706b23ab0001a34af2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24a45b646cd717dedaf","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981296573,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":38,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"8","question":"Name three things you and your closest friend or partner have in common.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":51,"rt":4306,"timeElapsed":1007720},{"subjectID":"n9x4mlaxxe","prolificID":"5c4d8d706b23ab0001a34af2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24a45b646cd717dedaf","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981312481,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":39,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"8","question":"Name three things you and your closest friend or partner have in common.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":15904,"timeElapsed":1023627},{"subjectID":"n9x4mlaxxe","prolificID":"5c4d8d706b23ab0001a34af2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24a45b646cd717dedaf","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981326775,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":40,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"8","question":"Name three things you and your closest friend or partner have in common.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":14291,"timeElapsed":1037922},{"subjectID":"n9x4mlaxxe","prolificID":"5c4d8d706b23ab0001a34af2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24a45b646cd717dedaf","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981335661,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":41,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"8","question":"Name three things you and your closest friend or partner have in common.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":8884,"timeElapsed":1046808},{"subjectID":"n9x4mlaxxe","prolificID":"5c4d8d706b23ab0001a34af2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24a45b646cd717dedaf","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981338780,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":42,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"8","question":"Name three things you and your closest friend or partner have in common.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":3114,"timeElapsed":1049927},{"subjectID":"n9x4mlaxxe","prolificID":"5c4d8d706b23ab0001a34af2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24a45b646cd717dedaf","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981344810,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":43,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"8","question":"Name three things you and your closest friend or partner have in common.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":39,"rt":6027,"timeElapsed":1055957},{"subjectID":"n9x4mlaxxe","prolificID":"5c4d8d706b23ab0001a34af2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24a45b646cd717dedaf","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981352725,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":44,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"8","question":"Name three things you and your closest friend or partner have in common.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":43,"rt":7911,"timeElapsed":1063872},{"subjectID":"n9x4mlaxxe","prolificID":"5c4d8d706b23ab0001a34af2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24a45b646cd717dedaf","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981364594,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":45,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"32","question":"Of all the people in your family, whose death would you find most tragic or difficult? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":10228,"timeElapsed":1075740},{"subjectID":"n9x4mlaxxe","prolificID":"5c4d8d706b23ab0001a34af2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24a45b646cd717dedaf","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981368520,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":46,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"32","question":"Of all the people in your family, whose death would you find most tragic or difficult? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":99,"rt":3923,"timeElapsed":1079667},{"subjectID":"n9x4mlaxxe","prolificID":"5c4d8d706b23ab0001a34af2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24a45b646cd717dedaf","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981373412,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":47,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"32","question":"Of all the people in your family, whose death would you find most tragic or difficult? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":47,"rt":4889,"timeElapsed":1084559},{"subjectID":"n9x4mlaxxe","prolificID":"5c4d8d706b23ab0001a34af2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24a45b646cd717dedaf","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981387951,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":48,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"32","question":"Of all the people in your family, whose death would you find most tragic or difficult? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":35,"rt":14536,"timeElapsed":1099098},{"subjectID":"n9x4mlaxxe","prolificID":"5c4d8d706b23ab0001a34af2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24a45b646cd717dedaf","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981397709,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":49,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"32","question":"Of all the people in your family, whose death would you find most tragic or difficult? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":40,"rt":9755,"timeElapsed":1108856},{"subjectID":"n9x4mlaxxe","prolificID":"5c4d8d706b23ab0001a34af2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24a45b646cd717dedaf","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981407086,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":50,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"32","question":"Of all the people in your family, whose death would you find most tragic or difficult? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":43,"rt":9374,"timeElapsed":1118233},{"subjectID":"n9x4mlaxxe","prolificID":"5c4d8d706b23ab0001a34af2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24a45b646cd717dedaf","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981410414,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":51,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"32","question":"Of all the people in your family, whose death would you find most tragic or difficult? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":44,"rt":3325,"timeElapsed":1121561},{"subjectID":"n9x4mlaxxe","prolificID":"5c4d8d706b23ab0001a34af2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24a45b646cd717dedaf","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981424074,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":52,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"32","question":"Of all the people in your family, whose death would you find most tragic or difficult? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":13656,"timeElapsed":1135221},{"subjectID":"n9x4mlaxxe","prolificID":"5c4d8d706b23ab0001a34af2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24a45b646cd717dedaf","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981430785,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":53,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"32","question":"Of all the people in your family, whose death would you find most tragic or difficult? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":53,"rt":6706,"timeElapsed":1141932},{"subjectID":"n9x4mlaxxe","prolificID":"5c4d8d706b23ab0001a34af2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24a45b646cd717dedaf","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981447545,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":54,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"29","question":"What, if anything, is too serious to be joked about?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":95,"rt":15434,"timeElapsed":1158692},{"subjectID":"n9x4mlaxxe","prolificID":"5c4d8d706b23ab0001a34af2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24a45b646cd717dedaf","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981453834,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":55,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"29","question":"What, if anything, is too serious to be joked about?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":38,"rt":6286,"timeElapsed":1164981},{"subjectID":"n9x4mlaxxe","prolificID":"5c4d8d706b23ab0001a34af2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24a45b646cd717dedaf","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981458106,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":56,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"29","question":"What, if anything, is too serious to be joked about?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":28,"rt":4267,"timeElapsed":1169252},{"subjectID":"n9x4mlaxxe","prolificID":"5c4d8d706b23ab0001a34af2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24a45b646cd717dedaf","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981470609,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":57,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"29","question":"What, if anything, is too serious to be joked about?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":46,"rt":12500,"timeElapsed":1181755},{"subjectID":"n9x4mlaxxe","prolificID":"5c4d8d706b23ab0001a34af2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24a45b646cd717dedaf","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981475628,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":58,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"29","question":"What, if anything, is too serious to be joked about?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":5016,"timeElapsed":1186775},{"subjectID":"n9x4mlaxxe","prolificID":"5c4d8d706b23ab0001a34af2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24a45b646cd717dedaf","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981482658,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":59,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"29","question":"What, if anything, is too serious to be joked about?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":42,"rt":7027,"timeElapsed":1193805},{"subjectID":"n9x4mlaxxe","prolificID":"5c4d8d706b23ab0001a34af2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24a45b646cd717dedaf","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981485709,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":60,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"29","question":"What, if anything, is too serious to be joked about?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":40,"rt":3048,"timeElapsed":1196856},{"subjectID":"n9x4mlaxxe","prolificID":"5c4d8d706b23ab0001a34af2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24a45b646cd717dedaf","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981491261,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":61,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"29","question":"What, if anything, is too serious to be joked about?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":41,"rt":5549,"timeElapsed":1202408},{"subjectID":"n9x4mlaxxe","prolificID":"5c4d8d706b23ab0001a34af2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24a45b646cd717dedaf","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981501377,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":62,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"29","question":"What, if anything, is too serious to be joked about?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":42,"rt":10112,"timeElapsed":1212524},{"subjectID":"n9x4mlaxxe","prolificID":"5c4d8d706b23ab0001a34af2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24a45b646cd717dedaf","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981521883,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":63,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"145","question":"Describe the most recent gift you received. Who was it from and what was the context?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":30,"rt":19132,"timeElapsed":1233030},{"subjectID":"n9x4mlaxxe","prolificID":"5c4d8d706b23ab0001a34af2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24a45b646cd717dedaf","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981530121,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":64,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"145","question":"Describe the most recent gift you received. Who was it from and what was the context?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":8234,"timeElapsed":1241267},{"subjectID":"n9x4mlaxxe","prolificID":"5c4d8d706b23ab0001a34af2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24a45b646cd717dedaf","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981534739,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":65,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"145","question":"Describe the most recent gift you received. Who was it from and what was the context?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":35,"rt":4614,"timeElapsed":1245886},{"subjectID":"n9x4mlaxxe","prolificID":"5c4d8d706b23ab0001a34af2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24a45b646cd717dedaf","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981542708,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":0,"trialIdx":65,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"Describe the most recent gift you received. Who was it from and what was the context?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMin":"STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMax":"PINEAPPLE","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":7966,"timeElapsed":1253855},{"subjectID":"n9x4mlaxxe","prolificID":"5c4d8d706b23ab0001a34af2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24a45b646cd717dedaf","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981552641,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":66,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"145","question":"Describe the most recent gift you received. Who was it from and what was the context?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":48,"rt":9929,"timeElapsed":1263788},{"subjectID":"n9x4mlaxxe","prolificID":"5c4d8d706b23ab0001a34af2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24a45b646cd717dedaf","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981559048,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":67,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"145","question":"Describe the most recent gift you received. Who was it from and what was the context?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":46,"rt":6404,"timeElapsed":1270195},{"subjectID":"n9x4mlaxxe","prolificID":"5c4d8d706b23ab0001a34af2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24a45b646cd717dedaf","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981587034,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":68,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"145","question":"Describe the most recent gift you received. Who was it from and what was the context?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":27982,"timeElapsed":1298181},{"subjectID":"n9x4mlaxxe","prolificID":"5c4d8d706b23ab0001a34af2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24a45b646cd717dedaf","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981591568,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":69,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"145","question":"Describe the most recent gift you received. Who was it from and what was the context?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":4531,"timeElapsed":1302715},{"subjectID":"n9x4mlaxxe","prolificID":"5c4d8d706b23ab0001a34af2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24a45b646cd717dedaf","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981598323,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":70,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"145","question":"Describe the most recent gift you received. Who was it from and what was the context?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":38,"rt":6750,"timeElapsed":1309470},{"subjectID":"n9x4mlaxxe","prolificID":"5c4d8d706b23ab0001a34af2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24a45b646cd717dedaf","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981601389,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":71,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"145","question":"Describe the most recent gift you received. Who was it from and what was the context?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":34,"rt":3063,"timeElapsed":1312536},{"subjectID":"n9x4mlaxxe","prolificID":"5c4d8d706b23ab0001a34af2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24a45b646cd717dedaf","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981610085,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":72,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"137","question":"How did you celebrate last Halloween?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":7332,"timeElapsed":1321232},{"subjectID":"n9x4mlaxxe","prolificID":"5c4d8d706b23ab0001a34af2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24a45b646cd717dedaf","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981613666,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":73,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"137","question":"How did you celebrate last Halloween?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":3577,"timeElapsed":1324813},{"subjectID":"n9x4mlaxxe","prolificID":"5c4d8d706b23ab0001a34af2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24a45b646cd717dedaf","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981616666,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":74,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"137","question":"How did you celebrate last Halloween?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":34,"rt":2997,"timeElapsed":1327813},{"subjectID":"n9x4mlaxxe","prolificID":"5c4d8d706b23ab0001a34af2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24a45b646cd717dedaf","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981626986,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":75,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"137","question":"How did you celebrate last Halloween?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":10317,"timeElapsed":1338133},{"subjectID":"n9x4mlaxxe","prolificID":"5c4d8d706b23ab0001a34af2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24a45b646cd717dedaf","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981640211,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":76,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"137","question":"How did you celebrate last Halloween?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":13222,"timeElapsed":1351358},{"subjectID":"n9x4mlaxxe","prolificID":"5c4d8d706b23ab0001a34af2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24a45b646cd717dedaf","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981645554,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":77,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"137","question":"How did you celebrate last Halloween?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":5339,"timeElapsed":1356700},{"subjectID":"n9x4mlaxxe","prolificID":"5c4d8d706b23ab0001a34af2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24a45b646cd717dedaf","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981648880,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":78,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"137","question":"How did you celebrate last Halloween?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":3323,"timeElapsed":1360027},{"subjectID":"n9x4mlaxxe","prolificID":"5c4d8d706b23ab0001a34af2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24a45b646cd717dedaf","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981654564,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":79,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"137","question":"How did you celebrate last Halloween?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":41,"rt":5680,"timeElapsed":1365710},{"subjectID":"n9x4mlaxxe","prolificID":"5c4d8d706b23ab0001a34af2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24a45b646cd717dedaf","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981659603,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":100,"trialIdx":79,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"How did you celebrate last Halloween?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled HAMBURGER","scaleTextMin":"HOTDOG","scaleTextMax":"HAMBURGER","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":5035,"timeElapsed":1370749},{"subjectID":"n9x4mlaxxe","prolificID":"5c4d8d706b23ab0001a34af2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24a45b646cd717dedaf","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981667060,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":80,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"137","question":"How did you celebrate last Halloween?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":37,"rt":7453,"timeElapsed":1378206},{"subjectID":"n9x4mlaxxe","prolificID":"5c4d8d706b23ab0001a34af2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24a45b646cd717dedaf","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981679364,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":81,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"71","question":"If you could live somebody else’s life for a day, whose would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":10724,"timeElapsed":1390510},{"subjectID":"n9x4mlaxxe","prolificID":"5c4d8d706b23ab0001a34af2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24a45b646cd717dedaf","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981686379,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":82,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"71","question":"If you could live somebody else’s life for a day, whose would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":7012,"timeElapsed":1397526},{"subjectID":"n9x4mlaxxe","prolificID":"5c4d8d706b23ab0001a34af2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24a45b646cd717dedaf","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981691941,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":83,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"71","question":"If you could live somebody else’s life for a day, whose would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":47,"rt":5558,"timeElapsed":1403087},{"subjectID":"n9x4mlaxxe","prolificID":"5c4d8d706b23ab0001a34af2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24a45b646cd717dedaf","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981699218,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":84,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"71","question":"If you could live somebody else’s life for a day, whose would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":7274,"timeElapsed":1410365},{"subjectID":"n9x4mlaxxe","prolificID":"5c4d8d706b23ab0001a34af2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24a45b646cd717dedaf","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981703198,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":85,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"71","question":"If you could live somebody else’s life for a day, whose would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":3977,"timeElapsed":1414345},{"subjectID":"n9x4mlaxxe","prolificID":"5c4d8d706b23ab0001a34af2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24a45b646cd717dedaf","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981725111,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":86,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"71","question":"If you could live somebody else’s life for a day, whose would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":21910,"timeElapsed":1436258},{"subjectID":"n9x4mlaxxe","prolificID":"5c4d8d706b23ab0001a34af2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24a45b646cd717dedaf","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981736315,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":87,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"71","question":"If you could live somebody else’s life for a day, whose would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":11197,"timeElapsed":1447462},{"subjectID":"n9x4mlaxxe","prolificID":"5c4d8d706b23ab0001a34af2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24a45b646cd717dedaf","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981742950,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":88,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"71","question":"If you could live somebody else’s life for a day, whose would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":39,"rt":6631,"timeElapsed":1454097},{"subjectID":"n9x4mlaxxe","prolificID":"5c4d8d706b23ab0001a34af2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24a45b646cd717dedaf","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981747799,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":89,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"71","question":"If you could live somebody else’s life for a day, whose would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":35,"rt":4845,"timeElapsed":1458945}]